KATE PRASOLEK

London E1 4RS | 07479929600

kate.prasolek@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kateprasolek https://artekatie.github.io/portfolio https://www.behance.net/artekatie

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop CC

Adobe in Design CC

Adobe Illustrator CC

Dotmailer/ Dotdigital

Adobe After Effects

Adobe XD / Figma

HTML5

CSS3

Bootstrap

Javascript & ¡Query

Git / Github

Google Web Designer

INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Eye for detail & professionalism
Can-do attitude & fast learner
Responsibility & reliability
Open mind & creativity
Commitment & consistency
Time management skills
Organisational skills
Ease of interpersonal contacts
Ability to teamwork

Customer service skills

PERSONAL PROFILE

A reliable, experienced in fast-paced environment designer with an easy-going, can-do attitude. Self-learner of HTML5 and CSS3.

Currently learning animations and website design. I am looking forward to working with a wide range of digital projects and consistently deliver a great experience for users and customers.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Graphic Designer at Wex Photo Video, London (Feb 2018 - Jan 2020)

As a part of small in-house team, I liaised with other departments to create, according to brand guidelines, a wide range of digital and print projects, such as:

- marketing emails, website banners, social media assets, GDNs
- adverts, business cards, flyers, point of sales, posters, brochures, catalogues, pull-up banners, signage, large format prints

I was also responsible for.

- supervising magazines' schedules, liaising with publishers
- maintaining and updating templates

Freelance Digital Designer, London (May 2016 - Feb 2018)

Creating logos, brochures, promotional digital and print assets, UI and website redesign.

Receptionist and Research Bank Worker at Poplar Harca, London (May 2015 - Nov 2017)

Reception duties, data administration, community projects.

Master Team Member at Paul UK (Jun 2013 - Feb 2015)

Supervising shift, organising displays and stock, handling orders, preparing sales plans & reports, customer service.

Saleswoman at Polkomtel SA (Oct 2010 - Dec 2012)

Phone customer service duties, selling and extending contracts.

Shift Supervisor at Pizzeria laPrimera (May 2009 - Sep 2010) Organising shifts, stock, deliveries and reports.

EDUCATION & TRAINING

I Google Web Designer, Adobe After Effects
 Dotmailer/ Dotdigital, Adobe Illustrator
 Adobe Dreamweaver, HTML emails

 HTML5/ CSS3, Javascript, jQuery

 Layout and Composition, Branding and Typography,

 Colour for Design and Art, Graphic Design Path,
 Adobe Photoshop and inDesign

 Psychology, master degree